[girls laughing
and screaming]
No.
No, go away.
I don't have time for this,
all right?
I have kids.
Regarde la fichue série
quand t'es censé le faire, d'accord ?
Amy.
Amy!
See?
Thanks a lot.
Way to go.
Amy!
Military school?
You said that you
weren't going back.
Pourquoi on s'est embêtés à se fiancer ?
Marry me
before you leave, dumbass (abruti).
You love me, right? Then
what's the point in waiting?
Get off the bus, Carl!
I love you!
[Nessa] Saw you took
the "For Rent" sign down.
[sighs]
It's about time I got
something of my own
for a change.
He come with the place too?
[Fiona] What should I say when
I talk about you
to other people?
Am I your girlfriend (petite amie)?
Are you a homosexual (homosexuel), Ian?
Y a quelqu'un d'autre qui en a marre
and want to get out of here?
[Geneva] It's on YouTube.
It's already got,
like, 1,000 hits.
Seriously?
[Kassidi]
He's like a prophet (prophète).
And he's super hot too.
Like hot gay Jesus.
So big,
and we do it in God's name.
[cheers and applause]
Mon Dieu est une tapette, un drogué,
a whore (pute)!
[explosion (explosion)]
♪ rock music ♪
Is he off his meds (médicaments)?
How the hell (L'enfer) would I know?
Everyone up!
I need sheets.
I need lots
and lots of sheets.
[crowd yelling]
Debbie !
Well, what would
the surgery (chirurgie) cost?
[Patel] It'll run you
at least $50,000.
[Frank] I was hoping there was
something I could do to help.
[Seery] We don't have
enough fathers
- on our PTA (pta).
- [Frank] Sign me up.
Pimp my ass.
Now tell me how much
you made last year.
Two grand, maybe,
and I don't pay taxes.
Ah!
Oh, you got a niece (nièce)?
La fille de ma sœur, Xan.
Any sign of Xan's mom (maman)?
Donne deux jours de plus à ce sac à merde.
Hey, why don't you come
stay with me for a couple days?
- That'd be cool.
- Cool.
Ces parents blancs, riches
et libéraux dans ton école,
we gotta take advantage (avantage)
of that.
They'll be gone.
We know the code.
You got the code, right?
[keypad beeping]
[alarm blaring]
Fuck!
- [phone rings]
- You gonna get that?
No.
[alarm blaring]
[siren wailing]
♪♪♪
♪ rock music ♪
♪ Think of all
the luck (chance) you got ♪
♪ Know that
it's not for naught (rien) ♪
♪ You were beaming
once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore (plus) ♪
♪ What is this downside (le revers de la médaille) ♪
♪ That you speak (parler) of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling (sentiment) ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Round up
the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that
they're not for naught (rien) ♪
♪ You were willing
once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore (plus) ♪
♪ What is this downside (le revers de la médaille) ♪
♪ That you speak (parler) of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling (sentiment) ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
[rats squeaking]
♪ Jack Berry's "Bad Dog"
playing ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Well, you can write
your name in the water ♪
[siren wailing]
♪ But you ain't hardly
got the sand ♪
♪ And you can lead
your sheep to slaughter ♪
♪ But you won't get
my helping (aidant) hand ♪
[groans]
♪ And you can love
your maker (fabricant) ♪
[phone chimes]
♪ From the top of every post
that you place ♪
♪ And you can weigh
your bacon ♪
♪ But keep your goddamn grease
off my plate ♪
♪ But you keep saying
I'm built for a cage ♪
- [Frank (franc)] Oh, shit.
- ♪ I have been all along ♪
♪ Good reason,
there's a real good reason ♪
♪ My bite is just as big
as my bark (aboiement) ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a bad dog ♪
♪♪♪
[zipper (fermeture éclair) zips]
Morning.
- You're up early.
- Yeah.
What you doing?
Retouches pour l'expert immobilier.
J'veux que ce soit parfait,
comme ça il dira que ça vaut
un milliard de dollars
and I get a big fat loan
for Ian's bail (caution).
Si tu gardes cette tenue,
t'auras tout ce que tu veux.
You think that's, uh (euh)...
Is that ketchup (ketchup)
or blood?
That could be either.
- Doesn't matter now.
- [chuckles]
We still going
to Costco later?
Yeah. Text me
when you're ready.
Okay.
Have a good day at work, dear (chérie).
[chuckles]
[phone ringing]
♪ Aaron (aaron) Rizzo's "Jericho"
playing ♪
Shit.
♪♪♪
♪ Say, Lord ♪
♪ Save my soul (âme) ♪
♪ Ain't got no love ♪
NOUVEAU MESSAGE - À EDDIE
TU REVIENS JAMAIS ?
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ That down in Jericho (Jéricho) ♪
♪ The ocean's dry (sec) ♪
♪ No water here
to wash (laver) me ♪
♪ Of my sins ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[horn blowing]
♪♪♪
Graveyarders, shift's (quart de travail) over!
Day crew, let's go!
speaking Spanish
speaking Russian
Équipe de nuit, vos chèques !
Thanks, Jacob.
Don't spend (dépenser) it all
in one place, Jugs.
- Breakfast (petit déjeuner)?
- Ooh, let's do it.
I'm starving.
- [moaning]
- ♪ funky music ♪
♪ Brother (frère), sister... ♪
♪♪♪
- Yeah?
- No, no.
♪ Superman (Superman) ♪
Okay.
D'accord, maintenant !
♪ Mr. Superman ♪
[both gasping]
♪♪♪
- [Greta sighs]
- [Frank laughs]
[both sigh (soupir)]
Whew.
[grunts]
See you later,
Greta's vagina (vagin).
Thanks for letting me
be of service to you.
[Greta laughs]
You're a funny (drôle) guy.
[both laugh (rire)]
Stay as long as you want.
I gotta get in the shower (douche).
Oh, I got you
a great shirt (chemise).
[shower (douche) running]
[grunts]
[phone chimes]
- ♪ jaunty music ♪
- [man humming]
♪♪♪
Hey, doll (poupée),
I gotta get going.
[Greta] Okay.
Text you the next time
Hal's out of town.
♪♪♪
You hear that, Hal?
You're a lucky (chanceux) guy.
Taught her a few new tricks.
Hope you like 'em.
You're welcome.
♪♪♪
- I've got you!
- I've (J'ai) got you!
- Got you!
- I've (j'ai) got you!
- I got you!
- I've (Je t'ai) got you!
Got you!
I've got you!
You don't have him,
Huntington.
J'ai pas une bonne prise, chef.
Are you trying to screw (baiser) me
out of becoming
- caporal-chef l'an prochain, asticot ?
- Non, chef !
Well, it sure as shit (merde)
looks like it.
Pourtant, on dirait bien !
Lâche ce cadet, minus !
Bon sang, c'était du figuré.
Sorry, sir (monsieur).
Sorry, Raul.
I have my year-end review with
the general this afternoon (l'après-midi).
Do you know what that
might be about, puke (vomir)-head?
Non, chef. Oui, chef.
De moi, chef ?
I've had the entire school year
à vous entraîner pour le combat,
and yet one big, fat turd (étron)
who can't keep up.
I'll do better, sir (Monsieur)!
Une chaîne a la force
de son maillon le plus faible.
and you are my weakest link!
Get out of my face!
Cadets--and Dave (dave)--
dismissed!
Corporal Gallagher
is on the move!
Left! Left!
Left, right, left!
Here we go again!
Hi, Carl!
I see you in there!
Walking down the avenue (avenue)!
Only two more days
until the end of school!
Mrs. Gallagher
is waiting for you!
- Gauche, droite !
- Je m'entraîne au Kegel !
- [Raul (raul)] Left, right, left!
- I love you!
There are three units
on this level
Il y a trois appartements à cet étage
et trois à l'étage du dessus.
Tous des locataires super fiables.
I put a new roof (toit) on
last year.
Uh, that was broken
when I bought the place.
I've been looking
for a matching piece.
That won't effect
the price, will it?
Just gotta take pictures
of what I see.
You must be so busy (occupé),
everyone trying
to refinance (refinancer)
before the rates
go up any more.
Been doing
ten of these a day.
Wow, that's a lot.
Yeah. Sure.
And you live around here,
in the city?
Uh, Schaumburg,
actually.
Oh.
It is so nice out there.
Have you been?
Uh, couple times.
What's the real estate like
out in, uh (euh), Schaumburg?
Nothing like what's
happening (le fait d'être) down here.
You grow (grandir) up there?
Yeah, yeah.
Born and raised.
Interesting.
It...[laughs]
It's not.
My husband (mari) and I,
we like it, though.
So what do you think
this place is worth?
$550?
$600 at least, right?
Gotta do the comps.
Don't see
any red flags, though.
Great.
Where's all the mechanical (mécanique)?
En bas, au sous-sol.
Ouais, c'est cette porte.
Mm-hmm (hmm).
[sighs]
♪ Funny (drôle), but when
you're near me ♪
♪ I'm in the mood for love ♪
♪ Bright (brillant) as the stars ♪
♪ We're under ♪
♪ Oh, is it any wonder (se poser des questions) ♪
Dinner is served.
♪ I'm in the mood ♪
♪ For love ♪
[zipper (fermeture éclair) zipping]
[vocalizing]
[coffee pouring]
[humming]
Bien le bonjour.
[normal voice] No time
for breakfast (petit déjeuner)...
J'ai pas le temps
pour un petit-déjeuner, domestique.
I'll just grab (prendre)
something to go.
Hmm.
speaking Spanish
L'argenterie disparaît,
ces derniers temps.
speaking Spanish
Commère.
♪ Hoo-hoo,
ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪♪♪
[engine turning over]
♪ Hey (Hey) ♪
♪♪♪
[man humming]
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Hoo,
ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
[knocking]
♪ Hoo-hoo,
ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪♪♪
Hey, Frank.
[Jules] Push.
Push.
Yo, Leo.
My cell,
five minutes.
No, thank you.
Oui, merci. J'ai besoin de me défouler.
I don't think so.
Since when do you get
a say in this, bitch (salope)?
Since I told him
that he gets a say in this,
bitch (salope).
They're on strike (la grève), remember?
C'était sérieux,
que nos putains sont en grève ?
Tant que t'acceptes pas
le respect sexuel mutuel,
ils reviendront pas.
- Let's go, Leo.
- [cries out]
Release him, jack-hole (trou)!
[men murmuring]
Fuck you
toi et ta grève des putains.
Bye, baby.
You're doing the right thing,
Leo.
I know, but I miss (s'ennuient) him.
Strength through
collective (collectif) action.
It's the only way
the oppressed
C'est comme ça
que les oppressés ont vaincu
les oppresseurs.
Strength, ladies.
Gallagher.
Visitor.
Yo, Jules, stand guard (garde).
I got it, boss (patron).
Strength.
T'es sûre que c'est bon si tu rates
l'école pour le mariage de Brad ?
Yeah, my teacher just said
Ouais. Ma maîtresse a dit qu'il faut
emmener un mot de ma maman demain.
Need me to write it?
Nan, je peux imiter sa signature.
Okay.
All right.
There we go.
And...
how do I look?
- Stupid (stupide).
- Well, good.
That's what I was going for.
Come on,
before you make me late.
♪ gong music and chanting ♪
[grunts]
I love yoga (yoga).
[phones chime (carillon)]
Ah.
What are you doing?
Réunion d'urgence de l'APE.
Pitié, pas les enfants.
On devrait peut-être accélérer.
Yeah.
Up you go.
Oh, God.
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
I'm close to getting
the bail (caution) money.
The court just did
an appraisal (évaluation) on my building.
- How soon?
- Tomorrow (demain), maybe.
I-I need a few more days.
Il y a de l'oppression partout, ici.
W-what are you talking about?
Je me casse le cul à te sortir
de ce trou à rats.
My work here is not done.
Je sauve les soumis
de leurs oppresseurs sexuels.
And I'm getting you
a $50,000 gift of freedom (liberté).
J'ai organisé une grève
contre les violeurs
qui terrorisent
les prisonniers homos et trans.
They take out
their feelings of...
d'infériorité et leur sexualité refoulée
sur nous, les queers.
Et ils ont une hygiène sexuelle affreuse.
A-are they giving you
your meds (médicaments) in there?
Je protège des agneaux sans défense
pour ne pas qu'on massacre
leur esprit et leur corps,
[door buzzes]
[girls snarling, screaming]
Don't break any bones, girls.
We can't afford (se permettre) the hospital.
V, why they got
so much energy now?
They were never like this
when Svetlana was here.
I think
they were scared of her.
Hell, I know I was.
[insistent pounding at door]
[Tommy] Open up, Kev.
We got a line out here.
- [girls] Whee (whee)!
- All right, I'm coming.
D'accord, j'arrive.
I'm coming!
[pounding at door]
[Tommy] Let's go,
while we're middle-aged!
[Kev] Calm down!
All right, girls,
just stay.
- Well, about time.
- Oh, relax (se détendre).
There's still 19 hours
left to drink (boire).
Let's go, yeah.
Let's go.
No, no, no, no, no no, no, no.
What are you--
Molly, how many times
have I told you?
You cannot (ne peut pas) bring dogs
in the bar.
Oh, come on, Kev.
I just need a shot and a beer (bière).
J'ai joué à la balle pendant deux heures
just to tire (pneu) them out.
All right, fine.
Make it fast.
It's just, I don't want to get
shut (fermer) down by the county.
Tes enfants dans une cage,
c'est ça qui va te faire fermer.
Plus de baby-sitter depuis
que Svetlana est partie.
Et plus de moments sexy, non plus.
Kev, no one needs to know
about our sex life.
[Kermit] I do.
Makes me not feel
Moi, si. Ma vie sexuelle
me paraît moins merdique.
[Kev] Hey, what's up, Debs?
[Debbie] Hey.
[Farhad] Pitcher of beer (bière),
please.
And a large Coke.
What, are you guys, like,
morning drinkers now?
Ha.
Your morning is our evening (soirée).
Every couple weeks,
Toutes les deux semaines,
on bosse de nuit. Ça craint.
Oh, can you cash my check
for me, V?
- How much is it for?
- $720.
Are you high?
We don't have
that kind of money
first thing in the morning.
We don't have that
kind of money
last thing at night.
Wait, $720?
De quoi tu parles ?
On a bossé les mêmes heures.
$18?
- Mm-hmm.
- An hour?
I make $15.
- Oh.
- Do you guys make $18 too?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
[scoffs]
Fucking Jacob.
♪ funky (funky) rock music ♪
♪ I'm a heat seeker,
I'm a revelator ♪
♪ If you're trying to stop me,
I'ma (I'ma) see you later ♪
♪ I'm a heat seeker... ♪
[girls growling]
♪ If you really want it,
you can get it ♪
♪ Treating every day like
the sun is never setting ♪
♪ If you really want it, then
you better go and get it ♪
♪ If you wanna
ha, ha, ha, ha... ♪
[horn honks]
♪ Don't stop
what you're doing, get it ♪
♪ If you want it,
go and get it ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪♪♪
Fuck.
Am I late?
Uh, no.
They're just getting started.
Oh, thank God.
I would never hear
the end of it from Cami.
T'es la demoiselle d'honneur ?
Yep.
Her sister (sœur), Tami.
Cami and Tami, huh (hein)?
Yeah, well, our parents,
Pami and Sami,
weren't very creative.
I'm fucking with you.
They're Bob and Kim.
Are you the best man?
Yeah, I'm Lip.
What's up with your hair?
Are you, like,
in the Marines or some shit (merde)?
J'étais défoncé.
Mes cheveux ont pris feu.
Je déconne. Je me suis endormi
avec un chewing-gum dans la bouche.
That's the most retarded thing
I've ever heard.
Dit-elle avec son bouffant
et son serre-tête de princesse.
I spent hours on this.
Well, you can't get
that time back, can you?
[laughs] Oh, I can't wait
J'ai hâte que cette putain
de cérémonie soit finie
so we can hit
the reception (réception).
et que la fête commence.
Je crève la dalle.
- Let's do this thing!
- After you.
Buzz off, will you?
What are you doing here?
I need you to do me a favor (faveur).
I...
- Salut.
- Salut, Frank.
Nice to see you again.
- It's been a while.
- Yeah.
Take this home with you,
will you?
Hide it someplace (un endroit) safe.
What's in it?
Un peu de beuh. De la cocaïne.
Quelques Oxys.
There's a PTA meeting.
It's probably best
not to bring that stuff
onto (sur) school grounds.
Hé ! Tu pourrais...
Doesn't sound like weed.
It's my salary (salaire).
Ever since you denied me
my big, fat score,
I've had to make money
the good old-fashioned way:
on my back,
taking what scraps I can
from your little friends'
parents.
I'm gonna pawn (mettre en gage) that stuff
after the meeting.
Yes?
[silverware clatters]
♪ militaristic (militariste) music ♪
♪♪♪
[Gene] Enter.
Repos, soldat.
Sir, I'd like to discuss
Chef, j'aimerais parler
de la promotion à caporal-chef.
I know it comes down
to me and Lawson
and that one of my men
is not up
to the high standards
demandé des cadets militaires.
but I promise (promesse) you,
if given that position,
I will get him there next year.
♪♪♪
What are your plans for
after graduation (l'obtention du diplôme), Corporal?
Sir?
C'est la tradition pour
les caporaux-chefs de se diriger
West Point?
Vous en avez la discipline.
Le goût de l'effort.
Obtenez la recommandation
d'un membre du Congrès ou sénateur.
You really think I could?
You'll have to handle (poignée)
your personal situation.
Il y a un civil dans une tente,
près des barbelés.
Les Gallaghers ont toujours attiré
les fous, chef.
My brothers have.
Sisters too.
My mother was crazy (fou).
♪♪♪
Bon, si vous pouvez
redresser votre peloton,
and personal issues, son,
vous avez de bonnes chances
de devenir caporal-chef l'an prochain.
Costco or bust (buste).
Hey.
Let me just get my stuff.
- Comment était Ian ?
- Plus fou que d'habitude.
Wants to stay in jail (prison).
Il a besoin de temps pour négocier
une grève entre les violeurs
et les agneaux.
No idea
what he's talking about.
C'est super extra dingue.
Yeah.
Anyway, here.
You left your coat (manteau)
at my place.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
All right, lads. I'm off.
I'll see you later, yeah?
All right, man.
See you.
[door buzzes]
Yo, gay Jesus!
You need
to release our hos (hos) now.
You ready to negotiate (négocier)
better conditions
for these children
of our Lord?
Hier soir, j'ai baisé mon lavabo.
- My balls are so blue.
- Yeah, that's right.
Then shall we talk,
de nous mettre d'accord sur
l'entretien des relations
with those we love
and care for?
Sure.
Whatever the fuck (putain) you say,
as long as I get
my ass eaten out.
[men murmuring]
All right.
Rompons le pain et buvons du vin ensemble.
♪ electronic music ♪
♪ Ow (ow) ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Smooth (lisse) ♪
♪ Smooth like butter ♪
I never thought
she'd stick (bâton) around.
Ah, well, you did the work.
You know?
You faced your demons.
[Brad] A kid (enfant) and the love
of a good woman
will do that to you.
Tu devrais essayer, un jour.
- Get out here...
- Let's go!
- ...and dance!
- Go get 'em.
No, no, no, if I'm doing this,
come on, you're coming with me.
- Come on, man.
- Come on.
Lip, we're doing
our nerdiest (le plus ringard) dance moves.
- Yeah?
- [Xan] Watch, okay.
Okay.
♪ Like a slippery slope ♪
♪ Oh, baby,
yeah, this is dope (dope) ♪
- I got one better.
- [Lip (Lip)] Yeah?
♪ Oh, boy, let's go ♪
- [laughter (rires)]
- Oh, my God.
All right, all right,
all right.
Bon, d'accord.
Peu importe comment je danse,
it's gonna be
the nerdiest (le plus ringard).
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Sure?
Okay.
- [Tami (tami)] Oh, Jesus.
- What? That's good!
That's awful (affreux).
- What's up?
- Nothing.
[Ted] Wanna dance?
Okay.
♪ Melt (la fonte) me up ♪
♪♪♪
C'est qui ce gamin ? Il a une barbe.
C'est l'effet des hormones
qu'ils mettent dans le lait.
Chillax, Grandpa.
She's having fun.
Come on.
Uh, where?
La demoiselle d'honneur et le témoin
couchent toujours aux mariages.
♪♪♪
♪ Smooth like butter ♪
Good afternoon (l'après-midi).
Thank you all
for coming in
on such short notice.
Earlier today,
I was contacted
by the county
health department.
- Des poux, encore ?
- Je préférerais.
[Len] Then what? I got
an open house in 30 minutes.
There's an epidemic (épidémie)
at our school.
- Measles?
- [Ed] It's because of those
anti-vaxxer French kids
you let in, isn't it?
It's not the measles.
C'est quelque chose de très délicat.
Une épidémie sexuelle.
In elementary (élémentaire) school?
That's the French.
- Ma fille a neuf ans.
- Et c'est une grosse salope.
Honey, stop.
I'm serious (sérieux).
You should see
Tu devrais voir ce que sa fille porte
quand elle sort.
It's called style.
Maybe your son
should take a few pointers.
Please, enough.
I'm not talking
about the children,
for God sakes.
I'm talking about you people.
Je parle de vous.
L'origine de l'épidémie vient
de cette association de parents d'élèves.
[woman] What?
[Seery]
I'll turn this over
to Dr. Jonathan Rosenbaum
from the county health board
to further explain (expliquer).
[Rosenbaum] Ah, thank you.
Comme indiqué, c'est un sujet sensible,
but one that we do not
take lightly (légèrement).
Over the past few weeks,
four people
have tested positive
pour de multiples genres
de MST virulentes.
The only thing these people
have in common
was this PTA group.
[Rosenbaum] In all my time
at the county
health department,
je n'ai jamais vu les symptômes
de ces trois maladies vénériennes,
chlamydia, gonorrhée et syphilis,
chez quatre patients à la fois.
Who the hell (l'enfer) are the four?
- Conneries.
- Je ne peux rien révéler,
but swift (rapide) action
must be taken
so we can learn
who these individuals
came in contact with
et qu'on puisse maîtriser l'épidémie.
Vous dites que ces quatre personnes
- given it to the rest of us?
- [Rosenbaum (rosenbaum)] Yes.
But that could only happen (il se trouve que)
from sex.
On n'attrape pas de MST sur les toilettes.
C'est absurde. Pardon, mais
j'ai un canal dentaire à traiter.
Sir, you're gonna stay
and be tested.
[Wells] Can't keep us here
against our will.
[Rosenbaum] Actually, I can.
The Illinois
Sexual Transmissible Disease
Control Act
states that we can order
the testing
and the isolation (l'isolement)
of an individual
to stop the spread (diffusion)
of an STD
until such time that the danger (danger)
to the public health
is eliminated.
That's the law.
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Folks!
- What is going on here?
As soon as everyone
is tested,
we can determine
who can leave
et qui a besoin d'antibiotiques
en intraveineuse. Merci.
- [man] This is--
- [man] What the--
- C'est...
- Qu'est-ce que...
C'est ridicule.
You pay Farhad more than me.
You know what, Jugs? I don't
even have you on the schedule
till tomorrow morning.
He gets $18 an hour.
Everybody does.
- I don't.
- Well, you're a girl.
What does that have to do
with anything?
Uh, you take
a lot of bathroom (salle de bain) breaks--
Faire pipi, les règles, tout ça...
J'ai chronométré.
- Quoi ?
- 24 minutes en tout,
sur une plage de huit heures.
That's because
your port-a-potties
C'est parce que vos WC portables
sont putain de répugnants.
Vous pissez partout sur le siège.
Je mets cinq minutes à tout nettoyer
et à faire mon nid avant
de pouvoir m'asseoir et pisser.
Way of the world, Jugs.
You don't like it,
find another job.
[grunting]
Wedding fucks are the best.
- You've done this before?
- Seven times.
You want my wedding pussy,
don't you?
Your version of dirty (cochon) talk?
Why, is it working?
Sure.
Ta queue me donne le vertige.
That a good thing?
Le couloir est en train de tourner, là.
Oh, hey (hey), you want me
to stop?
- [Tami (tami)] Ah...
- Fuck.
[Lip] Hey, are you all right?
Man.
I feel a lot better.
Okay, yeah, let's finish (finir)
this thing.
I need another drink (boire).
[dance music over speakers]
[sighs]
♪♪♪
Les connards qui sont infectés,
qui que vous soyez,
j'ai eu un coton-tige de 30 centimètres
enfoncé dans la queue.
Je comprends votre colère
ainsi que votre frustration,
et nous apprécions votre coopération.
At this time,
everyone has been tested.
[Rosenbaum] Thank you.
[clears throat (gorge)]
[Rosenbaum]
Uh, Donald and Eliza Watts,
Paula Dowd,
Leah and John Alperin,
Tod Carney,
Kate and Lina Thomas.
You're all free to go.
- Oui !
- Putain.
[indistinct chatter]
What about the rest of us?
You all tested positive.
[woman] No, that's impossible (impossible).
- C'est ridicule.
- Vous en êtes sûr ?
Nous devons retracer la toile
de vos partenaires
pour voir si quelqu'un d'autre
en-dehors de ce groupe a été infecté.
[Rosenbaum]
Look, I can't force you
Écoutez, je peux pas vous forcer
à me révéler vos partenaires sexuels,
but any information
you give us
could very well save lives.
♪ rock music ♪
♪♪♪
J'ai couché avec Irène Bragg.
Asshole!
Sale pute.
Ed.
Charlize Stewart.
[sighs]
What?
J'ai couché avec notre prof de tennis.
J'ai couché avec notre nounou.
[woman] I had sex
with my gynecologist (gynécologue).
I always fantasized
about having enough money
to stock up on toilet (les toilettes) paper.
Lofty goals.
Hey, when I was a kid (enfant),
we had to use
whatever (n'importe quoi) we could find.
Christmas napkins,
paperbacks,
coffee filters.
[phone buzzing]
You don't answer it?
No.
Got boxes to unpack (déballer).
I've got a bathroom (salle de bain)
to clean.
I clean it every week.
It's not that dirty (sale), is it?
- Derrière les toilettes ?
- Non.
No, and I never plan
on doing so.
Uh-huh (hein, c'est quoi ?).
L'estimation est arrivée.
Je peux payer la caution.
What?
Nothing.
[laughs]
Better not to get involved.
With me?
With your family.
Si t'es avec moi, t'es avec ma famille.
Parlons des toilettes sales.
You don't think
I should bail (cautionner) him out?
Didn't say that.
You didn't say anything.
It's like talking to a wall.
"Uh, excuse (excuse) me, Mr. Wall.
I just got
Pardon, M. Mur. Je viens de recevoir
l'argent pour la caution de mon frère.
Isn't that great?"
"Why, yes, Fiona.
That is fantastic (fantastique)!"
I doubt (le doute) the wall
would say that.
Yeah? Well, what would
the fucking
wall say, then?
Ian set a--a van on fire.
Il aurait pu tuer quelqu'un
dans son délire.
You said he's on and off
his medication (médicaments).
Donc je devrais pas
le faire sortir de prison ?
What if he doesn't show up
for his trial?
- He wouldn't do that.
- You sure?
He knows my ass
is on the line.
If he skips town,
you lose (perdre) all your money.
Could be put to better use.
- How?
- Don't know.
Invest in another
apartment (appartement) building.
Achète un café, un studio de yoga.
anything but your brother (frère).
Beverly.
[sighs]
My gardener (jardinier), Pablo.
[Beverly] I, uh (euh)--
I don't know his last name.
Uh, Kurt Alvarez.
Our pool guy.
And, uh (euh)...
Frank.
♪ upbeat (upbeat) rock music ♪
I slept with Frank.
So did I.
♪♪♪
Me too.
Yep.
Frank.
♪♪♪
J'ai couché avec Frank.
Frank.
♪♪♪
V, look how hard I am for you.
Ma queue est tellement dure
qu'elle soulève...
Kev!
Bon sang, V, t'étais censée
les mettre au lit !
Elles veulent pas dormir. J'ai essayé.
Tu leur as chanté la berceuse russe ?
A thousand (mille) times, and I read
to them,
and I rocked them
and I cuddled them
and I threatened them.
On devrait leur donner
de la crème de menthe.
- What?
- [Kev] All my foster parents
nous faisaient picoler pour qu'on dorme.
That's not
a great selling point.
[Kev] Then what are we gonna
do, then?
[children laughing]
♪ jaunty (jaunty) music ♪
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
What are you doing?
We're gonna go play fetch (aller chercher).
Ça a marché pour la dog sitter.
Maybe it'll work
for our kids.
♪♪♪
She's still at it.
♪ Carl (Carl), Carl, he's my man ♪
♪ If he can't fuck (baiser) me,
no one can ♪
À cause de cette sale folle
et de cet asticot merdeux,
j'aurai jamais cette promotion.
[Kassidi] I love you!
Whoo! Hi!
I see you!
♪ Carl (carl), Carl, he's my man ♪
♪ If he can't fuck (putain) me,
no one can ♪
♪ Carl (carl), Carl, Carl ♪
Okay, girls, you ready?
You ready?
Go get it!
Bring it back.
Run fast.
Good girl!
Okay, drop (laisser tomber) it.
Drop it.
♪ There's 50,000 reasons
for us to be free ♪
Now fetch (aller chercher)!
Good girl.
♪ Fifty (cinquante) thousand questions,
but they're all the same ♪
Move fast!
Use a lot of energy.
♪ Fifty (cinquante) thousand reasons
for us to be free ♪
♪ Come on, baby, that's a ♪
♪ Oh, baby, that ♪
♪♪♪
[laughs]
Hey, what are you
laughing about?
Video chatting with Ted.
He is so funny (drôle).
Say hi, Ted.
Hey.
Ah, hell (l'enfer), no.
Bye, Ted.
Hey!
[Lip] He has a beard (barbe).
Put on Paw Patrol.
[Lip] Oh!
Regarde tous ces trucs que Frank a piqué
aux mères de mes amis.
They know about it?
I don't think so.
Ah, you should pawn (mettre en gage) it, then.
Gonna give it back.
What, to Frank?
To my friends.
How are you even a Gallagher?
Le dîner est prêt.
[Debbie] Be there in a sec.
Why, what are you doing?
Mon patron dit que je pisse trop.
That's why I get paid
less than the guys.
Donc demain, je pisserai pas du tout.
Get paid less
just for showing us that.
Screw him.
Like guys don't piss (pisser).
It's total discrimination (discrimination).
Hey, I come bearing (Apporter) gifts.
Oh, uh (euh), Debs won't need any.
What is that?
It's best not to ask.
So...
I can get Ian's bail (caution) money.
[Debbie] That's great.
Yeah.
You guys don't think he would
skip out on me, do you?
Is he taking his meds (Les médicaments)?
Maybe not.
Is he gonna be able
to get his old EMT job back,
or go back to being
Gay Jesus?
Beats me.
Is he gonna pay back
his bail (caution)?
- Il va rembourser sa caution ?
- Je sais pas.
C'est pas important, si ?
How many times have we
bailed out family before?
Isn't that just the cost
of being a Gallagher?
♪ rock music ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪♪♪
V.
[whispering] V!
♪♪♪
[whispering] You did it!
It's go time.
♪♪♪
Thank you all for staying.
You're all to be commended.
Um, at this point,
you've all received
À ce stade, vous avez tous reçu
votre première dose d'Amoxicilline.
In four hours,
you'll receive another dose (dose),
followed by your final dose (dose),
four hours after that,
until you are no longer
a public health risk.
Have fun.
Comment se détendre
dans un endroit pareil,
quand on est piégés comme des rats ?
Si t'avais pas autant écarté les cuisses,
on en serait pas là.
You screwed just as many people
as I did.
[Sasha] I don't understand
why we can't leave.
It's not like we're gonna
have sex
and infect (infecter) the rest
of the world.
[Darren] You're definitely (définitivement)
not gonna have sex.
I mean, you don't want to have
sex more than quarterly (trimestriellement).
I have post-partum (partum)!
For three years?
Uh, in my experience,
she's got
quite an active libido (libido),
Mais ne nous battons pas.
We gotta make the best
of this situation.
The best of this situation?
T'as baisé toutes nos femmes, Gallagher.
Probably the reason
for this whole damn (Bon sang) thing.
[Len] Yeah.
Yeah, let's kill (tuer) him.
- [Wells] Yeah.
- [Frank] Oh, will you--
- Would you calm (le calme) down?
- Stop.
Careful.
Stop it.
Look at the bright (lumineux) side!
We're getting
free medical care.
Free medical care!
T'as détruit mon mariage.
I did you a favor (faveur)!
Mon pénis vous a peut-être
aidés à guérir, en fait.
Did you ever think of that?
De quoi tu parles, putain ?
Your bodies
are developing immunity (l'immunité)
to a horrible (horrible) disease
thanks to me!
Three horrible (horrible) diseases.
The fact that
you're all cheating
is a lot more serious (sérieux)
than a couple of silly (stupide)
que quelques maladies sexuellement
transmissibles absurdes.
I think you should use
this time
to reexamine (réexaminer)
your relationships.
There's nothing wrong
with our relationships.
Is that what you think,
Charlize?
Parce que tu m'as dit que tu te sentais
invisible sexuellement, face à Wells.
What?
That's bullshit (conneries).
She said you don't find her
attractive (séduisant)
since she had your child.
You saw the baby
come out of that thing,
and it grossed you out.
You gotta get over it, man.
Who the hell (l'enfer) are you,
to tell us what to do?
I'm the guy who supplied
your wives a service.
That's who.
You men have been
neglecting them.
Been off screwing other women
because it's more exciting,
but you have not put the time
into your marriages,
so I've had to do the work.
Thank God I'm great at sex.
It's probably 'cause
I've had a lot of practice.
A lotta practice.
Lotta, lotta, lotta practice.
I'm gonna kill (tuer) him.
What is your problem, man?
Will you--
[people shouting]
- Allez, tue-le, ce bâtard !
- Allez !
Get off!
Come on!
Look!
Look, Frank might have a point.
- He does?
- Yeah!
Listen to Darren.
The truth (la vérité) is,
Sasha,
I've been working too much,
and I haven't--haven't been
a very good husband (mari),
or a very good father,
and maybe we could just,
you know,
go somewhere (quelque part) and--
and talk about it.
- Fine.
- Yeah?
[Frank] Did you see that,
people?
La flamme de l'amour brûle de nouveau,
juste devant vous.
Does anyone else
want to talk,
try to come up
with a solution?
[Ed] I don't.
Irene can
Irène peut pourrir en enfer, je m'en fous.
You'll be right there
next to me.
Well, maybe some people need
a little longer to process.
Len,
we haven't had sex
in ages.
Honey, let's not air out
our laundry (la blanchisserie) here.
Len, please, let her--
let her continue.
You denied having sex
with every woman in here,
yet you tested positive.
That doesn't make sense to me,
Len.
They must have made a mistake (erreur).
Tell them about us, Len.
♪ guitar (guitare) music ♪
♪♪♪
Okay.
Fuck it.
♪♪♪
It's true.
[Len] Richard and I
are having an affair (liaison).
♪♪♪
Well, I didn't see
that coming.
♪♪♪
You see, folks?
Love is love is love.
[crying]
I'm so sorry (désolée).
♪♪♪
[crying]
[newscaster speaking
indistinctly on television]
♪ Ah (ah) ♪
♪ rock music ♪
♪♪♪
[phone chimes]
What are you doing?
I thought you were asleep (endormi).
Why do you have two phones?
It's for my mother.
It's an international phone.
Your mother's (mère) Patty?
Patricia, yeah.
Bullshit.
[laughs]
You don't believe me.
Should I?
You want me to call her?
It's early there.
She's old.
Il est tôt là-bas. Elle est vieille.
Elle se réveillera si t'insistes.
[sighs]
Non, c'est pas grave.
All this Ian stuff
is making you paranoid (paranoïaque).
Fine.
- Keep it.
- Why?
You don't trust me,
so take it.
If it rings, answer it,
Si ça sonne, tu auras
une agréable conversation avec ma mère.
Tell her I said hi.
♪ Danger (danger) Twins'
"Gotta Be Yourself" playing ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Mama (maman) always said
gotta be yourself ♪
♪ Gotta be yourself ♪
♪ Mama always said
don't worry, don't worry ♪
♪ About no one else ♪
♪♪♪
♪ We do it like we do it,
do it ♪
♪♪♪
♪ We do it
like we do it, yeah ♪
♪ Gotta be yourself ♪
♪ Gotta be,
gotta be yourself ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Daddy always tell me
that you gotta be tough ♪
♪ You gotta be tough (dur) ♪
♪ Everybody's (tout le monde est) gonna see
what you're made of ♪
♪ What you're made of ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- Salut !
- Salut.
J'ai une came cassée.
Grab that flashlight (lampe de poche).
Help me take a look.
Yeah, sure, sure.
You're in a good mood (humeur).
Je suis marié, putain.
That was the best day
of my life.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, looks like
the breather (reniflard) gear
took out the cam (came).
Eh.
Valves are bent (tordues) too.
I'm gonna write an estimate (devis).
Yeah.
So you and Tami hit it off
at the wedding.
[laughs]
Yeah, yeah.
She's cute (mignon).
Uh, we hooked up.
She was drunk (bourré).
Puked on me.
[laughs]
Le sexe sobre, c'est bizarre hein ?
Take her out
on a real date.
Go out for a steak (steak)
or something.
There's nothing like
a good woman to ground you.
She could be the one.
You never know.
Nah, no, I think I'm too busy (occupé)
for anything like that.
Yeah, because you spend (dépenser)
all your time
hanging (traîner) out
with that ten-year-old girl.
It's getting
kind of skeevy (bizarre), man.
Hey.
She doesn't have
anybody (n'importe qui) else.
[sighs]
Call DCFS, bro (bro).
Shit ain't your problem.
♪ rock music ♪
♪ I love my baby ♪
♪ That's why she has to die ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Mm, I love my baby ♪
♪ That's why she has to die ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Oh, I can't have
these feelings for you, girl ♪
♪ I'm (Je suis) not that type of guy ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Mm, I love my baby ♪
♪ You know I love her so ♪
[dialing phone]
♪ Mm, I love my baby ♪
[phone trilling]
♪ And that's why
she has to go ♪
Fuck (baiser)!
No, no, fuck.
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck (baise), fuck.
Ugh!
Fuck.
♪♪♪
♪ Ooh (ooh), oh, oh ♪
♪ Ooh (ooh), oh, oh, oh ♪
♪♪♪
[girls laughing]
They're not even
getting tired.
The dogs are, though.
[laughter (rires)]
I've got to get them
back to their owners
at some point, you guys.
Uh, Molly,
just ten more minutes, please.
On t'offre une bière et un shot.
Hey!
She's doing a public service.
[teacher and kids]
♪ How I wonder... ♪
Hey, look at that.
♪ Up above
the world so high... ♪
They're so well-behaved.
They're, like, the same age
as the girls,
and they can sing (chanter).
♪ Twinkle (scintillement), twinkle,
little star ♪
École maternelle.
[teacher and kids]
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[clears throat (gorge)]
Hey.
How's it going?
Can I help you?
Ouais, c'est Lip.
Tu sais, du mariage.
Oh, yeah.
'Sup?
Brad told me you worked here.
It's nice.
Okay.
Um...
Look, I thought maybe
you'd want to, uh (euh),
aller dîner quelque part,
ou un truc comme ça.
Oh, nah (nah).
I'm good.
You're--you're what?
Look,
Je suis sûre que tu déchires, parfois.
or not.
I don't know.
You're just...
really not that much fun.
You don't drink (boire),
you're all angsty (angoissé)
about some little girl,
Et tu baises super mal.
Je baise pas super mal.
Oh si, tu baises super mal.
Va te faire foutre.
Have you ever been
on the receiving end
of your fucking?
No.
So how would you even know
- Tu peux pas savoir.
- Ben c'est difficile
de ne pas super mal baiser
quand t'es dans une flaque de vomi,
à baiser une femme gargantuesque
dans un placard.
Whatever you need
to tell yourself
Peu importe, si ça t'aide
à dormir la nuit.
Pardon de pas être aussi bon
que les 73 autres témoins
you've had sex with,
all right?
Oh, you weren't.
No, not by a long shot.
That was probably
the worst lay
C'était sûrement le pire coup de ma vie.
- Bon sang !
- T'étais en mode tap, tap, tap.
- Tap, tap, tap.
- C'était même pas
to ask you out to dinner (dîner),
all right?
Brad made me do it.
I was just trying
to be a nice guy.
Nice guy?
Okay, well, then you
Sympa ? D'accord. Dans ce cas,
t'aurais du me baiser bien et fort.
'cause that would've (aurait) been
a nice guy.
You know, have a good life,
pukey (pukey).
Yeah, see you later,
jabby (jabby).
[shop bells jingle]
Hey, Nick!
[Debbie] You going
to the port-a-potty (le pot) again?
Third time
in the bathroom (salle de bains) today?
Whoo!
What's that,
about 12, 13 minutes, Jacob?
What's the deal
with you, Gallagher?
You haven't taken
a pee (pipi) break all day.
Shit, you're right.
Thanks for reminding me.
Gonna go right now.
♪ rock music ♪
♪♪♪
All done.
Hi.
Whatcha doing?
Je signe les papiers du prêt
pour la caution de Ian
and I don't want to hear
a word about it.
Not from me.
Pas un mot. J'apporte des burritos.
Chicken and bean (haricots)?
[Ford] Is that what you like?
Yes.
Then of course
that's what I got.
Thank you.
I will--
[laughs]
- J'accepte cette excuse burrito.
- Excuse ?
For keeping it a secret (secret)
you got two phones.
Oh, and here I thought
you were gonna apologize (s'excuser)
for snooping through my phones.
Yeah, no, not a chance.
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
Did you talk to my mother?
Nope, never rang.
Je l'ai fait tomber dans les toilettes,
j'espère qu'il fonctionne.
- Mmm (mmm).
- [laughs]
Took care of your problem,
Corporal Gallagher.
What problem is that?
Je voulais prouver ma loyauté
envers le peloton, chef.
De quoi tu parles, Cadet ?
Kassidi. Vous inquiétez pas, chef.
Personne retrouvera jamais le corps.
♪ rock music ♪
♪♪♪
I have good news.
Me too.
I can get the bail (la caution) money.
Our strike (grève) ended.
We were able to negotiate (négocier)
des accords de paix, sans violence.
I got approval (l'approbation)
to take a loan
- against my building.
- Now, some of the bangers
- en échange de l'immeuble.
- Certains violeurs sont lents
et comprennent pas très bien,
with the upbringing
they've had,
I'm not surprised.
Listen, if I bail (caution) you out,
are you gonna show up
for your trial?
Je sais pas où Iel va m'emmener, Fiona.
Who?
Shim.
C'est quoi, un Iel ?
[laughs]
I mean, we have no idea
if God's a she or a he,
do we?
Oh.
Shim.
♪ Whoa (whoa), I got out,
I got out ♪
♪ And not a moment (moment) too soon ♪
[Rosenbaum] Okay.
Mesdames et messieurs,
merci encore pour votre coopération.
Uh, we've contacted
your other sexual (sexuel) partners.
Uh, some of you
are gonna need to find
Certaines auront besoin
de chercher un nouveau prof de yoga.
Couple of you gentlemen
are gonna need
to look for a new assistant (assistant).
What if I stay with Richard
every Tuesday, Thursday,
et un week-end sur deux ?
- Parfait.
- Vous êtes un trouple ?
Yep.
Thanks, Frank.
Aww, that's just great.
[laughs]
Let's go, boys.
[sighs]
So,
we made it
to the other side.
Who knew STDs could bring
so much happiness (le bonheur)?
Hey, Gallagher.
I want to thank you
for showing me
Merci de m'avoir montré à quel point
ma femme est une putain déchaînée.
[gasps]
[groans]
[Irene] Call me, Frank.
♪ And not a moment (moment) too soon ♪
♪ Oh, not a moment (moment)
too soon ♪
♪ yeah ♪
Hey, Jacob!
Looks like I'm the only one
who didn't take
a pee (pipi) break today.
Guess you have no choice
but to pay me
the same as the guys.
$18 an hour, please.
Okay, fine.
You'll see it
in your next paycheck (chèque de paie), Jugs.
Thanks.
"Jugs"?
♪ jaunty (jaunty) music ♪
♪♪♪
What the hell (l'enfer) is this?
♪ I've been getting vibes
so fresh and clean ♪
♪ I can feel the sunshine (soleil)
calling me ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm feeling (sentiment) good,
feeling free ♪
♪ Running from my head
down to my feet ♪
♪ It's a beautiful day ♪
♪ Come out and play ♪
♪♪♪
♪ It's beautiful ♪